<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Week4Exercices2Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_goods_description">GoodsDescriptionActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"


    </string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="online_shopping">Online shopping</string>
    <string name="redline_store">RedLine store</string>
    <string name="shoes">shoes</string>
    <string name="shoes_id">Shoes</string>
    <string name="bicycles_id">Bicycles</string>
    <string name="watches_id">Watches</string>
    <string name="jackets_id">Jackets</string>
    <string name="com_like_id">Like</string>
    <string name="com_cart_id">Cart</string>
    <string name="communicate">Communicate</string>

    <string name="hypervenom">

        The Nike Hypervenom is a football boot that is manufactured by Nike. This type of boot
        is said to be for traction, power, and agility, designed for deceptive players. Therefore,
        it is endorsed/worn by players, notably forwards, such as Robert Lewandowski, Kylian
        Mbappé, Harry Kane, Edinson Cavani, Gonzalo Higuaín, Marcus Rashford, Mauro Icardi,
        Riyad Mahrez, Aubameyang and Thiago.[1][2]

In May 2013, the Nike Hypervenom Phantom was launched. It was launched and designed for Brazilian
        forward Neymar.[3] The boot is currently in its third version. There is one high-end model
        for the first version, the Hypervenom Phantom; whereas, there are two high-end models for
        the second version—the Nike Hypervenom Phantom II, which is a mid-cut variant and the Nike
        Hypervenom Phinish, the low-cut variant. However, Nike chose to discontinue the Nike
        Hypervenom Phinish from the third silo onwards due to confusion that the mid-cut version
        was better than the low-cut. The mid-cut version will be called "Hypervenom Phantom DF".[4]

The boot is available in Soft Ground (SG), Firm Ground (FG) or Artificial Ground (AG) versions in
        which all feature a glass nylon soleplate. There are also Turf (TF) and Indoor (IC)
        versions, in which the high-end model of these variants is the Nike HypervenomX Proximo.
        The SG soleplate features 6 removable aluminium studs, in which different studs with
        different lengths can be used, and 6 fixed bladed studs. The FG version has 12 bladed
        and conical studs. The AG model contains many circular and hollow studs, meant to have
        more pressure distribution and trapping air to reduce impact and prevent injuries.
    </string>
    <string name="lunar">The Lunar Gato 2 Premium is all about comfort. Combining extremely soft
        goat leather and Hyperfuse to make up the upper, along with Lunarlon foam cushioning to
        make for one of the most comfortable indoor soccer shoes that I’ve personally ever worn.
        From right out of the box the shoes are very comfortable, making for a shoe that requires
        very little break-in time. The goat leather upper provides a pillow-like softness against
        the foot while also maintaining a very flexible feel. When you pull the laces tight, you’ll
        find that the thin Hyperfuse section through the mid-foot provides some solid lock-down
        without feeling too restrictive. My one complaint regarding the comfort of the boot would
        be the mesh tongue. The tongue itself is nicely padded, but because the padding is so soft,
        it doesn’t provide much protection for your foot when pulling the laces tight, so if you
        tend to tie your shoes really tight, you may run into some minor issues with lace-bite.

Other comfort elements include a combination mesh and suede heel liner, providing a secure yet
        cushioned feel against the back of your foot. The Lunarlon outsole provides above average
        cushioning for an indoor soccer/futsal shoe, while still maintaining a low-profile. You’ll
        find that the back half of the shoe is by far the most cushioned, while the forefoot area
        of the sole is much less cushioned. The Lunarlon outsole provides a great mixture of
        cushion and responsive when running, which is hard to find from most indoor soccer shoes.
        The insole is also fully removable, providing great step-in comfort, as well as giving you
        the option to swap it out for something else if you choose to do so.</string>
    <string name="lunar_gato">The Lunar Gato 2 Premium is all about comfort. Combining extremely soft
        goat leather and Hyperfuse to make up the upper, along with Lunarlon foam cushioning to
        make for one of the most comfortable indoor soccer shoes that I’ve personally ever worn.
        From right out of the box the shoes are very comfortable, making for a shoe that requires
        very little break-in time. The goat leather upper provides a pillow-like softness against
        the foot while also maintaining a very flexible feel. When you pull the laces tight, you’ll
        find that the thin Hyperfuse section through the mid-foot provides some solid lock-down
        without feeling too restrictive. My one complaint regarding the comfort of the boot would
        be the mesh tongue. The tongue itself is nicely padded, but because the padding is so soft,
        it doesn’t provide much protection for your foot when pulling the laces tight, so if you
        tend to tie your shoes really tight, you may run into some minor issues with lace-bite.

Other comfort elements include a combination mesh and suede heel liner, providing a secure yet
        cushioned feel against the back of your foot. The Lunarlon outsole provides above average
        cushioning for an indoor soccer/futsal shoe, while still maintaining a low-profile. You’ll
        find that the back half of the shoe is by far the most cushioned, while the forefoot area
        of the sole is much less cushioned. The Lunarlon outsole provides a great mixture of
        cushion and responsive when running, which is hard to find from most indoor soccer shoes.
        The insole is also fully removable, providing great step-in comfort, as well as giving you
        the option to swap it out for something else if you choose to do so.</string>
    <string name="audi">The Audi E-bike is based on custom carbon fiber wheels and a full-suspension
        carbon fiber frame; even the front suspension forks are custom designed for this bike.
        The rims look very similar in design to those on the $80K Blacktrail, leading to
        speculation by some in the E-bike community that this bike was partially designed by
        PG Bikes, the company behind the Blacktrail.  Certainly at least the Audi ebike designers
        had the obscenely-priced Blacktrail in mind when they designed their bike.

The Audi E-bike also uses the same “Harmonic Drive System” as the Blacktrail, a highly regarded
        German design developed by Clean Mobile. Clean Mobile builds custom bottom-bracket drive
        systems for exclusive high end bikes made by innovative European companies such as KTM
        (see Egnition article here). Ironically Clean Mobile also went through an ownership change
        recently, first filing insolvency, and then being acquired by TQ-Systems GmbH, and
        switching most of its staff just last month.</string>
    <string name="swatch">Red translucent plastic case with a black silicone strap. Fixed black
        plastic bezel. Black dial with black hands with dot hour markers. Minute markers around the
        outer rim. Dial Type: Analog. Luminescent hands. Date display at the 3 oclock position.
        Automatic movement. Scratch resistant sapphire crystal. Pull / push crown. Transparent
        case back. Case diameter: 39 mm. Case thickness: 14 mm. Round case shape. Band width: 20
        mm. Band length: 8.5 inches. Tang clasp. Water resistant at 30 meters / 100 feet. Functions:
        date, hour, minute, second. Casual watch style. Watch label: Swiss Made. Swatch Sistem Red
        Automatic Black Dial Black Silicone Unisex Watch SUTR400.</string>
    <string name="jacket_red">A windbreaker, a windcheater, or a dutch-oven is a thin fabric coat
        designed to resist wind chill and light rain, making it a lighter version of the jacket.
        It is usually of lightweight construction and characteristically made of some type of
        synthetic material. A windbreaker often uses elastic waistbands, and/or armbands, and a
        zipper to allow adjustments for the current weather conditions.

Regular jackets, coats, etc. may include a type of windbreaker as an interlining that can be
        removed when desired. Windbreakers sometimes include a hood that may be removable and/or
        stowable. Many windbreakers may also include large pockets on the inside or the outside
        which allows belongings to be covered from weather such as light wind or rain as mentioned
        above. Windbreakers offer light to moderate insulating protection, more so than a sweater,
        but less than an overcoat.[1]
Windbreakers are primarily worn during the warmer seasons when wind or rain are expected, or as
        part of a layering strategy during colder seasons.[2] Brightly colored windbreakers may
        also be worn by runners as protection from the weather, and as a reflective garment used
        for safety.[citation needed] A 2012 study demonstrated that adding windbreaker pants and
        jackets offers a lightweight but effective means of delaying hypothermia if the user is
        outside walking and encounters unexpected low temperatures.[3]</string>
    <string name="rolex">Rolex SA (/ˈroʊlɛks/) is a Swiss luxury watchmaker. The company and its
        subsidiary Montres Tudor SA design, manufacture, distribute and service wristwatches sold
        under the Rolex and Tudor brands. Founded by Hans Wilsdorf and Alfred Davis in London,
        England in 1905 as Wilsdorf and Davis, Rolex moved its base of operations to Geneva,
        Switzerland in 1919.
Forbes ranked Rolex 64th on its 2016 list of the world's most powerful global brands.[1] Rolex
        is the largest single high end watch brand, producing about 2,000 watches per day.[2]

The company is owned by the Hans Wilsdorf Foundation, a private family trust.</string>
    <string name="hummer_bicycle">The new Hummer bicycle with its shimano 21 gearbox system make
        riding easier for you.It has V brake in rear and disk brake in front that brings more
        safety for riders. This bicycle is equipped with front shock- absorbers which facilitate
        riding. The folding option of this bicycle is placed in the middle of it and it gives more
        space in home and owner can easily put in his car trunk</string>
    <string name="runner_jacket">In 2016, the year of sport’s ultimate competition, Nike is
        celebrating its foremost apparel icon: the Nike Windrunner Jacket. Designed in the late
        70s, the silhouette has been a fixture on medal stands and city streets ever since.
        Seen on everyone from distance runners to spinning b-boys, the jacket continues to
        evolve and serve as a collaborative canvas, a practice that picks up in 2016: The Year
        of the Windrunner.​ </string>
    <string name="hyper_jacket">
Nike Hyperadapt 1.0
The Nike HyperAdapt 1.0 is the first self-lacing shoe made directly available for retail.
        The design of the footwear was executed by Tinker Hatfield accompanied by Mark Parker,
        who was heavily involved in the development. Utilizing an electro adaptive lacing system
        abbreviated as "E.A.R.L.", the sneaker technically autonomously conforms to the figuration
        of one’s foot.[1] On December, 1st 2016, they were officially released in limited quantity
        for $720.[2] The Hyperadapt has been released several times since the initial release date
        in extremely small quantity.[3]</string>

</resources>
